<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Application</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string-array name="summary">
        <item>Design Patterns in Java gives you the hands-on practice and deep insight you need to fully leverage the significant power of design patterns in any Java software project. The perfect complement to the classic Design Patterns, this learn-by-doing workbook applies the latest Java features and best practices to all of the original 23 patterns identified in that groundbreaking text. Drawing on their extensive experience as Java instructors and programmers, Steve Metsker and Bill Wake illuminate each pattern with real Java programs, clear UML diagrams, and compelling exercises. You\'ll move quickly from theory to application―learning how to improve new code and refactor existing code for simplicity, manageability, and performance.</item>
        <item>System developers have used modeling languages for decades to specify, visualize, construct, and document systems. The Unified Modeling Language (UML) is one of those languages. UML makes it possible for team members to collaborate by providing a common language that applies to a multitude of different systems. Essentially, it enables you to communicate solutions in a consistent, tool-supported language.Today, UML has become the standard method for modeling software systems, which means you\'re probably confronting this rich and expressive language more than ever before. And even though you may not write UML diagrams yourself, you\'ll still need to interpret diagrams written by others.UML 2.0 in a Nutshell from O\'Reilly feels your pain. It\'s been crafted for professionals like you who must read, create, and understand system artifacts expressed using UML. Furthermore, it\'s been fully revised to cover version 2.0 of the language.This comprehensive new edition not only provides a quick-reference to all UML 2.0 diagram types, it also explains key concepts in a way that appeals to readers already familiar with UML or object-oriented programming concepts.</item>
        <item>Portable and precise, this pocket-sized guide delivers ready answers for the day-to-day administration of SQL Server. Zero in on core support and maintenance tasks using quick-reference tables, instructions, and lists. You\'ll get the focused information you need to save time and get the job done—whether at your desk or in the field!</item>
        <item>Author Jason Ostrander walks developers through the different choices available on their way to creating a well-designed application for Android. While building a simple application, Jason works through the basics of Android UI development including layout, event handling, menus and notifications. The author then shows the proper way to load and display images, create advanced dialogs and progress indicators, add animation, and how to build custom UI elements. Jason discusses the proper way of adding interaction through gestures and the advanced graphical options available using Canvas, Renderscript and OpenGL. Finally, he discusses tablet development, the unique differences between phone and tablet UI, and the new APIs available to tablet developers.</item>
        <item>Objective-C has become the standard programming language for application development on the iOS and OS X platforms. A powerful yet simple object-oriented programming language that\'s based on C, Objective-C is widely available not only on Apple platforms but across many operating systems, including Linux, Unix, and Windows. Programming in Objective-C provides the new programmer a complete, step-by-step introduction to the Objective-C language. The book does not assume previous experience with either C or object-oriented programming languages, and it includes many detailed, practical examples of how to put Objective-C to use in your everyday programming needs.The fifth edition of this book has been updated to cover the new features in Objective-C programming introduced with Xcode 4.4 (OS X Mountain Lion) and Xcode 4.5 (iOS 6). It also includes coverage of Automatic Reference Counting (ARC) and shows how to take advantage of the Foundation framework\'s rich built-in library of classes and provides an introduction to iOS programming.</item>
        <item>Learning Agile is a comprehensive guide to the most popular agile methods, written in a light and engaging style that makes it easy for you to learn. Agile has revolutionized the way teams approach software development, but with dozens of agile methodologies to choose from, the decision to "go agile" can be tricky. This practical book helps you sort it out, first by grounding you in agile\'s underlying principles, then by describing four specific--and well-used--agile methods: Scrum, extreme programming (XP), Lean, and Kanban. Each method focuses on a different area of development, but they all aim to change your team\'s mindset--from individuals who simply follow a plan to a cohesive group that makes decisions together. Whether you\'re considering agile for the first time, or trying it again, you\'ll learn how to choose a method that best fits your team and your company.</item>
        <item>If you are new to Unix, this concise book will tell you just what you need to get started and no more. Unix was one of the first operating systems written in C, a high-level programming language, and its natural portability and low price made it a popular choice among universities. Initially, two main dialects of Unix existed: one produced by AT and T known as System V, and one developed at UC Berkeley and known as BSD. In recent years, many other dialects have been created, including the highly popular Linux operating system and the new Mac OS X (a derivative of BSD). Learning the Unix Operating System is a handy book for someone just starting with Unix or Linux, and it\'s an ideal primer for Mac and PC users of the Internet who need to know a little about Unix on the systems they visit.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_detail">DetailActivity</string>
</resources>
